Words, music, arrangement by Masaru Yamaguchi
Song: Yu Yamaguchi
Please subscribe to our channel!
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Here we are in Fukuoka!
What was that? Why am I turning it?
I'm just a little disturbed by all this today.
OK
so much (little)
Today, we have a little bit of, you know, of our makeup, and we have a little bit of free time.
That's right.
Let's go eat ramen!
Yeah! Yes!
Fukuoka is known for its tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen.
Sure, it's squirming.
Looking for clear tonkotsu ramen, as the time of day is also the time of day.
What do you mean, clear tonkotsu ramen?
There's a transparent tonkotsu ramen.
No, you don't.
There is, actually.
There's one in Ginza, but the visual there has a bit of an impact on me.
I see you have one in Ginza to go eat now, how's that?
No, but Hakata Ramen.
I see.
In case you're wondering, it's the real deal.
If you can eat the ramen chosen by Craft Presents.
(often in neg. sentences) (not) a waka, haiku, etc.
But I was sleeping all the way up until a few minutes ago. Are you okay with your sleeping habits?
I'm fine.
Take a good look. I'm pretty swollen.
Stop!
I'm fine.
If you do that, you're not cured.
I'm not going to get better.
Then let's go eat ramen.
I still have it.
Oh well.
Well, I guess sleeping habits are part of the charm.
oh!
good day (daytime greeting)
Yes, sir.
OK
Arrived?
Arrived.
I like it better when you come here.
This is it?
I'm eating it for the first time.
I'd like to try it.
Let's eat, let's eat
Shall we go?
Clear Tonkotsu Ramen
It's pork bone ramen.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
I would like to eat this.
expression of gratitude before meals
Wow! Pork bones! Pork bones!
Horse!
It's light, but it's still very good! Pork bone broth!
It tastes like something I would want to drink!
What?
Mr. Sakazaki, by the way, Fukuoka is
Do you have any projects, memories?
Memories?
But when I was a research student
Takada Ramen.
I was turning Fukuoka and writing about it.
He wants you to sign it.
still
The fact that they're crossing over...
Husband, with both
Ten minutes later...
Is it signed?
oh, yes!
Very nice.
delicious
Cabos peel facing left.
Oh, this way.
amazing (e.g. of strength)
expression of gratitude before meals
Oh yummy!
It's different again.
Wow, I love the flavor I put in it!
I think I'll try another one.
What are you going to do?
Can we go inside?
I'm in.
even
I've got a live show coming up.
In good shape.
therefore
oh, yes!
Right now, we have a member who is ahead of us.
To its members.
Pullman's Ramen.
I would like to bring it as a souvenir.
therefore
That was a delicious meal (said after meals)
Something about Fukuoka's tourist attractions.
You haven't been there much.
local content
Maybe I haven't been there much.
Fukuoka's tourist attractions are...
Did you go?
former
Like a pig purse.
Eating Kakuni Manju or something like that.
I did.
I went with Takada.
In the fan club, in case you were wondering.
It's going up.
So next time.
When I went to Fukuoka on tour or something.
I'd love to spend a day touring.
After making the rounds.
And the satellites, the live ones.
I thought it would be easier to see the sights.
Because I don't think it's too difficult in terms of tourism.
I hope you'll tour with us and enjoy Fukuoka with us.
We will enjoy ourselves and our fans will enjoy themselves, and I didn't say we would do such a bus tour.
We'll do it with us.
Maybe you might do it.
I might do that, though.
I'd like to go to a fishing port in Fukuoka or something.
Fukuoka Fishing Port
fishing harbour
Because mentaiko is famous?
There's a fishing port, because it's right on the ocean.
I like fishing ports, like Fukuoka's fishing ports.
I love fishing ports so much.
Oh, you have it, don't you? You have it, don't you?
We're getting there. We're getting there. We're getting there.
Well, here we are. We're backstage.
Backstage at the Beliebe, backstage, not backstage.
I would like to give you a souvenir.
What are you guys wearing? Aren't they wearing makeup?
good
please
good morning
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I bought some souvenirs.
souvenir
I was totally happy.
Thank you.
What did we eat?
Clear Tonkotsukotsu Ramen
Clear Tonkotsu Ramen?
Tonkotsu Ramen is fine.
I wonder what he'll say.
transparently
Clear and pork bone ramen.
Like the flavor is refreshing.
oh, yes!
Clear.
And that's what we do at home and for fun.
By daring to keep it.
Thank you.
Can I make it at home?
I can make it at home.
There's also Kyun-kun.
whee
I was going to go out for ramen normally after this.
We'll see about that.
in that case
You're coming with me.
How many bowls am I supposed to eat?
I'm not making it today.
I mean, have fun when you get home.
I see.
Let's get it straight.
I had it from the soup.
I usually get it from the normal
Then add green onions.
Then put the skin down.
go and squeeze
please
Thank you.
Good luck at Lilly today!
That kind of thing is also very important
Let's go for it.
So, thank you very much for Fukuoka!
Thank you very much.
We are looking forward to seeing you in Fukuoka in the spring tour!
Please come visit us!
I'll be waiting for you!
I'll be waiting.
bye-bye
Oh man, shampoo.
Oh, did you turn it?
unbelievable
Yay!
How hard did you choose your noodles?
It's not a balicata.
I like the balicata, too.
after all
It's like "Kata" followed by "Kata".
What's next for Balicata?
No more wire.
Don't eat any more wire.
What did you put on the dumplings?
I'm done.
Soy sauce.
Soy sauce? No raayu?
Yes, yes, yes!
Great, I knew you'd be there.
Oh, no?
No, this much.
Wow, it's great!
expression of gratitude before meals
with a flat forehead
Eating damage is different.
Oh my God, I'm so happy.